 {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which is the tallest mountain in Earth?",
        "options": ["MT.Everest", "Annapurna", "Mt.k2", "Kanchunjunga"],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the most popular tourist destination in Nepal?",
        "options": ["Kathmandu", "Biratnagar", "Pokhara", "Kanyam"],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "To visit Pathivara temple from Biratnagar via Illam how many districts you have to cross?",
        "options": ["Two", "Three", "Four", "Five"],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country is Nepal bordered in the South?",
        "options": ["India", "Bangaladesh", "China", "USA"],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the highest altitude lake in the world?",
        "options": [
          "Tilicho",
          "Gokyo",
          "Vesuvius",
          "Toba"
        ],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Where was PN shah born?",
        "options": ["Biratnagar", "Gorkha", "Kathmandu", "Pokhara"],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "If 5+5 becomes 15, Give me correct answer for 12+12?",
        "options": [
          "29",
          "20",
          "36",
          "40"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "What?",
        "options": [
          "Running an effect",
          "Passing props",
          "Updating state",
          "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "I am always hungry. The thing i touch instant turn red. What am I??",
        "options": [
          "Tomatoes",
          "Red ink",
          "Fire",
          "None"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
        "options": [
          "When updating the state will be slow",
          "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
          "When the state update should happen faster",
          "When the new state depends on the previous state"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "I am an odd number. Take away one letter, and I become even. What number am I??",
        "options": [
          "3",
          "5",
          "7",
          "9"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "What does kemish love mostly for his dinner?",
        "options": ["cauli", "roast", "simple rice", "momos"],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "I am an odd prime number. If you double me and add 1, you get a square number. What number am I?",
        "options": [
          "1",
          "3",
          "5",
          "7"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
        "options": [
          "True",
          "It depends on the dependency array",
          "False",
          "In depends on the code in the effect"
        ],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "If day after tomorrow and tomorrow(Nikorsi) is tuesday, what was the day three before from today?",
        "options": [
          "Monday",
          "Tuesday",
          "Wednesday",
          "Thursday"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 20
      }
    ]
  }
  